<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hankou</title>
    <link>https://hankou.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hankou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.148.0</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:13:13 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://hankou.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>持仓 Position</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/investment/position/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:13:13 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/investment/position/</guid>
      <description>WindRider Stock Portfolio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>风舵1号 (WindRider I)  /// 指数</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/investment/windrider-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:15:03 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/investment/windrider-1/</guid>
      <description>商品期货分形摆动策略实盘</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Job Might Last a Lifetime</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/a-job-might-last-a-lifetime/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/a-job-might-last-a-lifetime/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On a ThinkPad that had been in service for over 15 years, the code for &amp;ldquo;Wind Rudder No. 1&amp;rdquo; finally ran successfully. Three months of back-testing data showed considerable profitability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope had never felt so real. In a life spent stumbling through the better part of my years, all rehearsals had taken place within textbooks written by teachers. No matter how many times I verified the calculations, they were always other people&amp;rsquo;s stories, other people&amp;rsquo;s scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading is Still Useful After All</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/reading-is-still-useful-after-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/reading-is-still-useful-after-all/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Guanshidun, three breakfast shops stood open, side by side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &amp;ldquo;Old Jar Pickled Cabbage Hot Dry Noodle Shop&amp;rdquo; was the one right in the middle. The owner cooking the noodles was a young man wearing a disposable black mask. While boiling noodles, he chatted with the customers, asking if the property management of the used car market across the street had given them any trouble lately. The customers owned a stall in the market and came here for breakfast every day. The small speaker in the shop played a classic pop earworm from days gone by: &amp;ldquo;Come, come, have a drink, don&amp;rsquo;t stop until you&amp;rsquo;re drunk&amp;hellip; can&amp;rsquo;t keep the hurried love by your side&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return to the Fields of Hope</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/return-to-the-fields-of-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/return-to-the-fields-of-hope/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Teacher Yu&amp;rsquo;s New Year&amp;rsquo;s concert was overflowing with a joy reminiscent of the song, &amp;ldquo;On the Fields of Hope.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The baritone, puffing out his slightly portly frame, controlled his vocal cords with a warm, polished smoothness as he gazed deeply toward a distant hometown. A duet was performed by a man and a woman whose combined ages exceeded 130 years; they meticulously mimicked every gesture of the idols on the cassette covers of their youth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s Not Leanness, It’s Laxity</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/its-not-leanness-its-laxity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/its-not-leanness-its-laxity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sister Tony always has a heavy hand when cutting hair. The electric clippers start from the nape of the neck, pushing upward right against the scalp. You can feel the cold touch of the metal; it’s nothing if not clean and sharp. After she finishes buzzing, she politely asks Lin Song, &amp;ldquo;Is this length okay?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s fine.&amp;rdquo; You’ve already shaved off the hair on the left side; whether it&amp;rsquo;s okay or not, that&amp;rsquo;s how it is. It’s not as if you can leave the hair on the right side unshaved, can you? When walking out of a barbershop, if anyone can tell at a glance that you’ve just had a haircut, it was definitely cut by a &amp;ldquo;Student Tony&amp;rdquo; just entering the trade. But if the hair looks natural, as if it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been cut at all, it was likely the handiwork of a &amp;ldquo;Master Tony.&amp;rdquo; To have Master Tony cut your hair, you have to pay an extra ten yuan on top of the member&amp;rsquo;s price.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better a witty fool that a foolish wit</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/investment/guide-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/investment/guide-1/</guid>
      <description>Thinking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Man Sunbathing at the Crossroads</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-man-sunbathing-at-the-crossroads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-man-sunbathing-at-the-crossroads/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He stood there at the intersection, motionless, facing the center of the crossroads no matter which way the traffic light turned green. The morning sun shone on his slightly weathered cheek, illuminating his faint smile. It turned out he was standing there to bask in the sun. When the tall buildings ahead blocked the sun as it moved from east to west, he would walk to the opposite corner where the sunlight still reached, and continue his sunbathing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Increasingly Unruly World</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/an-increasingly-unruly-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/an-increasingly-unruly-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Following days of gloom, the sun finally revealed itself in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just past 8:00 AM, the Starbucks barista began scrubbing the ground at the entrance with a bucket of water. Wearing only a green short-sleeved T-shirt, his thin frame faced the north wind, yet he seemed impervious to the cold. A slightly chubby girl sat leaning on a chair brushing her teeth; the shop hadn&amp;rsquo;t opened yet, and the U-lock still hung on the handle of the glass door.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serious Writing: The Highest Form of Intellectual Discipline</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/serious-writing-the-highest-form-of-intellectual-discipline/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/serious-writing-the-highest-form-of-intellectual-discipline/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Writing is never about you. It is about whether you can use words to change the world—even if it&amp;rsquo;s just a small corner of the minds of a few key people. This may sound cold, but it is the most authentic rule of academic writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your teachers are not your real readers; they read your work out of obligation. The real-world reader owes you nothing. Similarly, the clichéd goal of &amp;ldquo;filling a knowledge gap&amp;rdquo; pales in comparison to the reality of infinite knowledge expansion. What truly matters is solving the &amp;ldquo;expensive&amp;rdquo; problems that readers actually care about. This is precisely why interdisciplinary writing is so fraught: if you cannot define &amp;ldquo;who the reader is,&amp;rdquo; writing becomes like shooting blindly in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Talk to Strangers</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/dont-talk-to-strangers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/dont-talk-to-strangers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There was dew under the eaves in the early morning. Disturbed by the waving hand of the breakfast stall owner, a fly fell into a freshly filled bowl of doufunao (tofu pudding). The owner&amp;rsquo;s hands were quick. The spoon, which had just been used for white sugar, deftly scooped the fly out and flicked it onto the sidewalk. She then smoothly pushed the bowl toward an old man who had just paid. The old man, usually quiet, was not the least bit muddled. &amp;ldquo;Why are you giving me the one with the fly?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;This one isn&amp;rsquo;t for you. Take the one next to it.&amp;rdquo; The owner moved the &amp;ldquo;cleaned&amp;rdquo; bowl of tofu pudding to the side of the bucket, leaving it for the next customer who paid.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing New Under the Sun</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/nothing-new-under-the-sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/nothing-new-under-the-sun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The morning glow emerged. Standing at the intersection, he saw the rooftops of distant high-rises, bathed in golden sunlight.
Up early, Lin Song pulled a thick fleece vest over his shirt and went out to wander the streets. In the vegetable market, people were hurriedly buying groceries. Some rode electric bikes to take their children to school, others queued in cars for the commute to work or delivered goods to businesses. Breakfast stalls were firing up their stoves. Lin Song strolled along with his hands in his pockets, appearing out of place.
The laptop&amp;rsquo;s power light was stuck on. Lin Song forced a shutdown, and then it broke. It would no longer boot up. This machine had rehearsed its end countless times: a new battery, a new hard drive, a new keyboard, and, in the last two months, a new power cord. Years ago, Lin Song had started backing up the laptop&amp;rsquo;s data intermittently, but it had never suffered a significant failure, running stably day after day. Eventually, he forgot to back up the data again.
This time, the destruction came like a landslide.
Lin Song booked an appointment with a computer repair shop on Taobao and went there, carrying his laptop. He still felt it was just a minor circuit issue, that a simple reconnection would bring his laptop back to life.
Two customers were at the counter, picking up their computers and checking if the repaired machines could withstand the test of continued work. Three technicians were busy at their respective workstations, heads down.
The technician nearest the counter took Lin Song&amp;rsquo;s laptop, asked briefly about the symptoms, and began to disassemble it. &amp;ldquo;Just so you know, the repair fee will be around 200 yuan.&amp;rdquo;
After finishing the diagnostic, he reassembled the dismantled machine and returned it to Lin Song, saying:
&amp;ldquo;It can&amp;rsquo;t be fixed. The CPU is dead. It&amp;rsquo;s not worth repairing.&amp;rdquo;
It was a troublesome situation, but Lin Song accepted this reality calmly. He looked at the mountain of computer components piled up in the shop and asked the lady boss, though he already knew the answer:
&amp;ldquo;Do you sell second-hand computers here?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Yes. What kind are you looking for?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Something on the same level as my current machine. Do you have anything?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Yours is a classic model. This black one is similar, from &amp;lsquo;21.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;How much?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;1800. If you use your original hard drive, 1650.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Can my old hard drive still be used?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;We can take it out. Just put it in an external enclosure and you can use it.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;What operating system is on it?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Windows 10.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ll take this one.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Scan the QR code on the counter.&amp;rdquo;
Lin Song left the machine that had been with him for nearly ten years. The lady boss reluctantly valued it at 100 yuan for recycling. Lin Song headed home with his new laptop.
Even as the stock market soars, all everyone talks about after dinner is the economic downturn. What&amp;rsquo;s the logic in that?
In the first half of 2025, Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s revenue increased by 13% year-over-year, and its earnings per share grew by 35.5%. Nestlé announced it would cut 16,000 jobs over the next two years; its 2025 first-half report showed a 1.8% year-over-year decline in global sales and a 10.3% plunge in net profit.
The general meaning is that social wealth is already overflowing. The main owners of this wealth control the most competitive industries. To protect the competitive strength of their industries, the powers that control wealth will not give more opportunities to the weak, bottom-level economic participants. Thus, capital, through its powerful ability to regulate the allocation of market resources, restricts the paths for small and medium-sized industries to gain greater competitiveness.
And so, one can see a booming stock market advancing side-by-side with a withered individual economy. If you&amp;rsquo;re a small business, you might as well be content with your lot. As long as you can open your shop every day, you can earn some surplus, however small. It&amp;rsquo;s the same principle as stock trading: trading time for space. The size of your operation dictates the language you speak. The real economy and the financial market speak different economic languages.
Zoran Mamdani—the son of a film director and a Columbia University professor—achieved an upset victory on Tuesday, being elected the 111th Mayor of New York. In the world&amp;rsquo;s most important financial city, over a million people chose to support him, something unseen in half a century.
His rival suffered two disastrous defeats in just five months; all previous hopes now feel like a distant dream. Many expressed they were tired of the stalemate maintained by traditional powers for decades.
The young people say, &amp;ldquo;Illusion is now a thing of the past.&amp;rdquo;
The monk Tang Sanzang endured countless hardships to retrieve the scriptures, envying the Western Paradise. But one day, upon ascending the high platform where demons danced wildly, he realized it was merely a clumsy imitation of the original.
He finished his last delivery. At the T-junction of Dingzi Bridge, he waited for the last traffic light. Once he got onto the South Second Ring Road, he could go straight home.
He had been out since early morning. It was another exhausting day. By the time he got home, it was already past time to make dinner. Lin Song decided to just take a nap on the sofa.
He slept past eight o&amp;rsquo;clock. Lin Song took a yellow windbreaker from the coat rack and put it on. This jacket, bought on Taobao, had a huge kangaroo silhouette printed on the back. With this logo, he could go to the &amp;ldquo;Mr. Rice&amp;rdquo; downstairs and eat his fill for just ten yuan.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Happy Ending for All</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/a-happe-ending-for-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/a-happe-ending-for-all/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a decade of fluctuations, the Shanghai Composite Index has once again touched the 4,000-point mark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Dow Jones Index has hit a historic high. The UK&amp;rsquo;s FTSE Index has hit a historic high. Japan&amp;rsquo;s Nikkei Index has hit a 34-year high. Global stock market indices saw an overall increase of 9.1% in the first half of the year, setting a new record.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A soybean is a legume, about one centimeter in size. It can be eaten in its pod as edamame, or processed into tofu, soy milk, and other products. But that&amp;rsquo;s not why it has become one of the most profitable commodities in the world. Soybeans are rich in fat and protein, making them the primary feed for most of the world&amp;rsquo;s livestock.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Least Trustworthy Thing</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-least-trustworthy-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-least-trustworthy-thing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Fasting.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Level 1 Care.&amp;rdquo; These were rather stimulating terms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the first day of the &amp;ldquo;Golden September, Silver October&amp;rdquo; peak season, Lin Song checked himself into a hospital bed on the fourteenth floor of the Houhu campus. The lights in the ward were turned off just after 8 PM, but it was impossible to sleep. He closed his eyes, pulled the covers up to his shoulders, and forced himself to try. But it was contrary to his wishes. A kaleidoscope of colors spun endlessly in his mind, like a carousel. He could only watch and wait.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scar Heals, the Pain Is Forgotten</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-scar-heals-the-pain-is-forgotten/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-scar-heals-the-pain-is-forgotten/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lin Song felt as if his sky had caved in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ordinarily, almost no one worries that the sky might one day collapse. Everyone understands that in this world, there are always people taller than themselves who will be the first to prop up that falling sky. On a leisurely holiday, lying on the park grass and gazing up at the sky, the wind is gentle, the sun is beautiful, and the sky has not caved in. All fantasies are of a boundlessly wonderful future: a job with more income, a bigger house, a more comfortable vacation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yearning</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/yearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/yearning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The gods always protect those who peacefully endure hardship. As for those who unfortunately suffer calamity, it can only be said that their own fate is to blame, not that the gods failed to protect them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The above sentiment was a conclusion reached by Su Dongpo and his family as they journeyed down the river through the Three Gorges. He believed that if a man cannot control his body and mind, he cannot control his soul. Lin Song, however, believed that even if a man controls his body and mind, he may not be able to control his soul.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A-Shares Have no Starting Line, Only People Sneak Away</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/a-shares-have-no-starting-line-only-people-sneak-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/a-shares-have-no-starting-line-only-people-sneak-away/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The sun provides the Earth with energy, but it is the monsoon that determines our environment. Whether it brings scorching drought or favorable rains, the monsoon arrives as promised, cycling tirelessly, year after year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If capital is the sun of the market, then consensus is its monsoon. Capital is the fundamental force that drives the market, but only when its participants reach some form of consensus can a real trend take shape.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Flat Tire or a Liquidated Account: That Is the Question</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/a-flat-tire-or-a-liquidated-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/a-flat-tire-or-a-liquidated-account/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was another heart-pounding Monday morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At 11:11 AM, the ChiNext board touched 2782 points, a new high for the past three years. Nearly a full year had passed since the last wave of public euphoria, and this time, the revelry had already lasted for two months. For the past three weeks, it had been a topic of hopeful conversation for everyone, regardless of whether they followed the market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some sat in the shade of a tree, dreaming of the next new high; others, in their air-conditioned rooms, quietly reduced their positions. Some were rushing into the market, not caring whether they understood how it worked—a rising price is something everyone can comprehend.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scallion, Ginger, and Edamame with &#34;June Yellow&#34; Crabs</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/scallion-ginger-and-edamame-with-june-yellow-crabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/scallion-ginger-and-edamame-with-june-yellow-crabs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Even as Wuhan’s weather entered the &lt;em&gt;Chushu&lt;/em&gt; (End of Heat) solar term, the sweltering heat remained unbearable. The cicadas in the trees, having chirped through the entire summer, now sounded faint and weary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scorching sun, high in the sky, was obscured by a thick blanket of mackerel-scale clouds, and the world instantly dimmed. Lin Song quickened his pace, planning to take advantage of the shade to slip under the overpass. But man proposes, God disposes. Just as he reached the middle of the road, the clouds were blown away, and the violent sun reappeared, its fiery rays beating down on the asphalt, making him feel dizzy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team Building In a Barbecue Restaurant</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/team-building-in-a-barbecue-restaurant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/team-building-in-a-barbecue-restaurant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tuesday is members&amp;rsquo; day at the Total gas station. If you go on this day, you can save a few dimes per liter, and the station also gives you a few discount coupons to use for your next fill-up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lin Song hadn&amp;rsquo;t driven all day, but to avoid missing today&amp;rsquo;s deal, he decided to make a trip to Total after the sun went down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After filling up his Peugeot 508 and parking it in the underground garage, Lin Song sat in the car and scrolled through his phone for a while. According to a Nikkei report, Japan&amp;rsquo;s imports of Chinese cosmetics had jumped to third place, behind only South Korea and France. Chinese brands were appearing in Japanese department stores and drugstores. Apparently, complaints about being &amp;ldquo;uneasy with Chinese cosmetics&amp;rdquo; had decreased.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worse Than a Cold: Life’s Helplessness</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/worse-than-a-cold-lifes-helplessness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/worse-than-a-cold-lifes-helplessness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Early on a weekend morning, Lin Song had to go to Gaoqiao Fifth Road to pick up some goods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He had received the call from the freight yard on Thursday notifying him the shipment had arrived. He had delayed for a day; thankfully, there weren&amp;rsquo;t many heavy trucks on the Third Ring Road on a Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the Gusao Shu interchange viaduct, on the ramp turning from the Airport Expressway toward Gutian Second Road, a black Volkswagen tailgated Lin Song&amp;rsquo;s Peugeot 508. He could clearly see the numbers on the license plate in his rearview mirror—obviously an unsafe following distance. Lin Song hugged the inside line of the lane, gently pressed the accelerator, and swiftly rounded the circular ramp. By the time he straightened out, the black Volkswagen was no longer in sight. The feeling of being pressured finally eased.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Locked Mailbox</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-locked-mailbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-locked-mailbox/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He hadn&amp;rsquo;t checked the mailbox in his building&amp;rsquo;s entryway for a long time. Remembering that an important piece of mail was supposed to arrive recently, Lin Song rummaged through a miscellaneous box in his bookcase and was relieved to find the mailbox key still there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Three days ago, Lin Song had peered through the mail slot, scouting it out. There appeared to be an EMS envelope inside. But he had long since lost the habit of carrying keys, so he didn&amp;rsquo;t know for sure what was in there.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You Blocking Your Own Way?</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/are-you-blocking-your-own-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/are-you-blocking-your-own-way/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Everyone has their own &amp;ldquo;soul breakfast.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Lin Song, it’s pan-fried buns, which must be paired with two fried eggs. If a breakfast shop only serves braised eggs, Lin Song considers them insincere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sharing a table with Lin Song were a young daughter and her earnestly instructing mother. The daughter had wanted pan-fried buns; the mother had ordered steamed dumplings. When the girl saw the pan-fried buns in Lin Song&amp;rsquo;s bowl, a look of disappointment crossed her face, as she had none.
&amp;ldquo;You just eat your food properly. Finish these hot dry noodles, then have two steamed dumplings.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;A fly, a fly! Shoo it away, shoo it away!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll go see if the steamed dumplings are ready yet.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I want to eat from the big bowl. And I want diced pickled radish.&amp;rdquo;
A waitress, clearing tables, repeatedly shouted into her headset microphone:
&amp;ldquo;Special deal today! Shumai are buy one, get one free!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Su Dongpo the Influencer</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/su-dongpo-the-influencer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/su-dongpo-the-influencer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The shopping mall had set up temporary stalls in the open space by Entrance 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Special Clearance on Books,&amp;rdquo; 9.9 yuan/jin (approx. 500g): &lt;em&gt;The Encyclopedia of Healthy Recipes&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;A Guide to Food Pairings and Prohibitions&lt;/em&gt;.
&amp;ldquo;Children&amp;rsquo;s Book Clearance,&amp;rdquo; 20 yuan/jin: &lt;em&gt;Encyclopedia of Chinese Geography&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Andersen&amp;rsquo;s Fairy Tales&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Calabash Brothers&lt;/em&gt;.
&amp;ldquo;Novel Clearance,&amp;rdquo; 22 yuan/jin: &lt;em&gt;Nezha: Past Stories of the Three Realms&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Details of Law&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Grave Robbers&amp;rsquo; Chronicles&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lin Song circled the bookstall three and a half times, scanning the titles one by one. Among the books piled on the tables, there were a few scattered ones he had read.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peel the Tomatoes</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/peel-the-tomatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/peel-the-tomatoes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An important sign that summer is about to end is that by Saturday morning, the food delivery platforms have eased up on their promotions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lin Song parked his car in the underground garage. Before turning off the engine, he glanced at the time on the display: ten past five. Still enough time to make dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Fingerprint error!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sharp alert from the smart lock startled Lin Song. Every time he opened the door, he was very careful to cover the sensor completely with his thumb. Could it be that his hands were too dirty after moving cardboard boxes all day?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Guy Who Put the Ticket on His Car</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-guy-who-put-the-ticket-on-his-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-guy-who-put-the-ticket-on-his-car/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Venting is a base emotion. Lin Song dislikes it when people get forceful and aggressive in their interactions. Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s because, over the past few years, he has been so worn down by such overbearing attitudes that he feels his own lung capacity has diminished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At noon, after dropping off Xiao Lin at the train station, he went to a client&amp;rsquo;s office to settle a payment. Coming down from the elevated departure level of the station, Lin Song began to wonder how he would kill the next two hours until his client&amp;rsquo;s office opened at two. It was too hot to stay out under the sun. The underground parking at the mall was only free for thirty minutes, which, after accounting for the time to drive in and out, wasn&amp;rsquo;t even long enough for a nap. Maybe he could find a diner on a small side street, have lunch, and enjoy two hours of free air conditioning. That seemed like a good option.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silhouette of the City</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/silhouette-of-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/silhouette-of-the-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As expected, the orange high-temperature warning arrived on schedule, like a gilded invitation for the entire city to partake in a grand sauna. For all those not required to clock in at an office, the strategy for escaping the heat was strikingly uniform: flock to the shopping mall, that modern oasis of steel and concrete, to righteously share its free air conditioning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sun had just crossed the horizon, the morning light yet to fully dispel the city&amp;rsquo;s slumber, when figures already began to gather at the mall&amp;rsquo;s entrance at half-past nine. It had become an unspoken ritual. In the mall&amp;rsquo;s atrium, the tables and chairs intended to attract customers for coffee shops and bubble tea stalls now served as the exclusive domain of the city’s elders—the Grandpas Wang and Auntie Lis. They were the earliest &amp;ldquo;residents&amp;rdquo; here, sitting quietly with the unhurried poise of age. The businesses seemed to have grown accustomed to this special group of &amp;ldquo;patrons.&amp;rdquo; During off-peak hours, the staff would carefully navigate around their napping forms, reluctant to disturb the tranquility that belonged to them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We are all reconciling with life in our own way</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/we-are-all-reconciling-with-life-in-our-own-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/we-are-all-reconciling-with-life-in-our-own-way/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At the intersection beneath the overpass, the road surface, worn out from years of neglect, was once riddled with potholes. Drivers who frequented this route would instinctively steer around the sunken manhole covers to avoid scraping the undercarriage of their cars. After the summer rains, the eroded roadbed, repeatedly crushed by heavy vehicles, became even more bumpy and unbearable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last week, the intersection was repaved with fresh asphalt, the depressions were filled, and a new crosswalk was painted at the widest point.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This summer, we are all pretending it is not hot</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/this-summer-we-are-all-pretending-it-is-not-hot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/this-summer-we-are-all-pretending-it-is-not-hot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For 30 consecutive days, the maximum temperature in Wuhan has exceeded 38°C (100.4°F). For a month, the high temperatures have had perfect attendance, never absent, never late.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the sweltering heat of July, some chose to escape to southeastern Hubei. But who would have known that deep in the Dabie Mountains, it was just as historically hot as Wuhan? During the day, swirling clouds of mist felt like a steamer; at night, air conditioning was a must. The teachers who went to the mountains to escape the heat this summer all felt they had escaped for nothing. Since they had to use air conditioning anyway, wasn&amp;rsquo;t it better to be back in Wuhan, sprawled on their own couches, eating watermelon and scrolling through their phones, free and at ease?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitness and Self-Cultivation</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/fitness-and-self-cultivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/fitness-and-self-cultivation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On a Saturday afternoon, the gym is at its quietest. Sunlight slants through the massive floor-to-ceiling windows, casting bright patches on the dark gray rubber floor. The air is a mixture of scents—the cold, metallic smell of the equipment, a faint hint of disinfectant, and the subtle trace of evaporated sweat. The weekday evening hustle is gone, replaced by an off-peak tranquility, as if a soothing rest note has been placed at the end of a long, strenuous week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Journey Home</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-journey-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-journey-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was sunny when he set out. After crossing the Dabie Mountains, the clouds in the sky began to thicken. As he approached Fuyang, a few raindrops even splattered against the windshield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the past, when traveling on inter-provincial expressways, you had to swap your IC toll card at each provincial border, settling the toll for the completed section before starting anew in the next province. Every business trip left Lin Song with a pile of toll receipts to file for reimbursement. This time, however, he truly understood what a &amp;ldquo;seamless journey&amp;rdquo; meant. He collected his IC card at Hankou North, entered the G42 Shanghai-Chengdu Expressway, and didn&amp;rsquo;t settle the toll until he exited at Yingshang East from the Chuzhou-Xincai Expressway. There were no intermediate charges—it was a single, uninterrupted trip.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cautious Journey</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/a-cautions-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/a-cautions-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At just past five in the morning, the breakfast shop behind the station was already open for business. The young man frying buns looked up with surprise as Lin Song walked past his storefront.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lin Song had to make a trip to Fuyang this morning for his first meeting with a client. To avoid getting sunburned during the long drive, he had deliberately worn a long-sleeved shirt. He had planned to buy four buns from the Kechen Baozi Shop for breakfast, but when he saw that a single bun from this shop was bigger than two from the Dehua Restaurant, he quickly told the owner that two meat buns and one vegetable bun would be enough. The three large buns cost seven yuan in total.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Without the Pre-Made, There Is No Everyday</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/without-the-pre-made-there-is-no-everyday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/without-the-pre-made-there-is-no-everyday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly, there was no one seeking refuge from the heat in the entrance passage of the Shiqiao Metro Station. As Lin Song descended on the escalator, he could feel that the air conditioning in the station seemed to be off. On the concourse level, in front of the Zhou Hei Ya duck neck stall, a notice was pasted on the bright yellow construction barrier: &amp;ldquo;Construction Hazard, Do Not Approach.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s breakfast was &lt;em&gt;reganmian&lt;/em&gt;. The new girl at the counter asked every customer as a matter of routine, &amp;ldquo;Is there anything you don&amp;rsquo;t want in it?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;No string beans.&amp;rdquo;
A mother asked the little boy, who was also having &lt;em&gt;reganmian&lt;/em&gt;, what else he wanted.
&amp;ldquo;A cup of soy milk. Remember to get a warm one.&amp;rdquo;
After instructing his mother, the little boy started singing, &amp;ldquo;A-ba-zi, a-ba-zi, a-ba-zi&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scratching an Itch Through a Boot</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/scratching-an-itch-through-a-boot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/scratching-an-itch-through-a-boot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Summer vacation was in full swing, and grandparents had become the main force in childcare. The grandmothers&amp;rsquo; specialty was taking the little ones to the mall to cool off. They&amp;rsquo;d find an open area with a large TV, and the old and young would sit down in rows. The TV played old cartoons on a loop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A film like &lt;em&gt;Godzilla vs. Kong&lt;/em&gt; held no appeal for them. The children lost interest after a couple of glances, and the elderly had no idea who the monsters were fighting, much less why. The kids much preferred watching Princess Elsa from &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt; sing her enchanting songs. When the beautiful Elsa danced, the children became exceptionally well-behaved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buddha has both the Fierce-Eyed Glare of a Vajra and the Gentle, Downcast Gaze of a Bodhisattva</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/buddha-has-both-the-fierce-eyed-glare-of-a-vajra-and-the-gentle-downcast-gaze-of-a-bodhisattva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/buddha-has-both-the-fierce-eyed-glare-of-a-vajra-and-the-gentle-downcast-gaze-of-a-bodhisattva/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In October of 1996, Lin Song and his colleagues went to Zhengzhou on a business trip. The weather was cool and pleasant. After finishing their official duties, they decided to use the spare time before their return journey to visit the Songshan Shaolin Temple. By then, nearly fifteen years had passed since Lin Song, in the prime of his youth, had watched Jet Li&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Shaolin Temple&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lin Song remembered it was a weekday. Aside from seeing the sign for a martial arts school at the entrance, there weren&amp;rsquo;t many tourists at the temple. It was a spontaneous trip, so they hadn&amp;rsquo;t brought a camera. They used their memories of the movie as their travel guide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Endless Road</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/an-endless-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/an-endless-road/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He left the house too early, his morning appetite not yet awakened. Lin Song went to the Dehua Restaurant to get two orders of &lt;em&gt;xiao long bao&lt;/em&gt; and two fried eggs, drizzling some light soy sauce over the yolks. He took the food with him in the car, ready to comfort his hollow stomach whenever hunger decided to strike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the summer, it seems human skin can perform photosynthesis. As long as you give it some water, you can go all day without thinking about food. The afternoon is when children are supposed to take their naps; summer afternoons are sweltering and boring. The TV stations no longer loop reruns of &lt;em&gt;My Fair Princess&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Journey to the West&lt;/em&gt;, so children can take advantage of their grandparents&amp;rsquo; naptime to scroll through all sorts of videos on their phones.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Stage to Theater</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/from-stage-to-theater/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/from-stage-to-theater/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At noon, Chen Peisi’s star power failed to draw a larger audience for his film, &lt;em&gt;The Stage&lt;/em&gt;. Screening Room No. 2, located near the ticket check, is one of the larger theaters in the cinema. Even so, there were fewer people in the audience than there were opera fans in the movie itself. After accounting for the couple who walked out midway, the vast theater felt even more sparse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film&amp;rsquo;s original score left little impression, mainly because &lt;em&gt;The Stage&lt;/em&gt; is set against the backdrop of the Peking Opera classic &lt;em&gt;Farewell My Concubine&lt;/em&gt;, and thus, most of the film’s music was occupied by traditional opera melodies. The choice of lyrics for the closing credits song—Wang Anshi&amp;rsquo;s poem, &lt;em&gt;To the Tune of Gui Zhi Xiang: Musing on the Past at Jinling&lt;/em&gt;—was quite an elegant touch. Its final line, &amp;ldquo;To this day, the singing girls still from time to time perform the songs of a fallen dynasty,&amp;rdquo; could perhaps be gifted to those film critics incapable of understanding the movie.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lit Candle</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-lit-candle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-lit-candle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was a strange day; no matter where he sat, Lin Song could smell a thick odor of sweat. It was a summer smell he knew well. Back in middle school, he’d wear the same jersey for an entire afternoon of ball games, and after practice, he’d just toss it in the equipment room, only to put it on again the next afternoon. It was an age of utter indifference.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulated Coolness</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/simulated-coolness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/simulated-coolness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The best legacy a restaurant that has closed for good can leave to a shopping mall is its wide assortment of tables and chairs. The vacated stalls can&amp;rsquo;t find new tenants right away, so they become temporary leisure areas.
On this hot summer day, in an air-conditioned mall, as long as there are enough seats, there will be enough customers coming to escape the heat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The grandpas and grandmas, brothers and sisters who come to enjoy the cool, bring their cell phones and occupy every empty seat. If a bench hidden behind a barricade is wide enough, lying down for an hour or two is also a fine option. A small personal bag for a pillow, and you have a perfect afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Director&#39;s Dog</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-directors-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-directors-dog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After raining for half the night, it finally stopped. The east-facing window did not greet an early-rising sun. The air was clear and transparent. Along the horizon, thick cumulonimbus clouds curled, letting a faint morning glow seep through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Room 7 on the sixth floor is being renovated. Debris from dismantled old cabinets litters the elevator. You have to watch your step coming in and out to avoid a nail. Just after 8:30 a.m., the impact drill started, sending vibrations through the entire building and giving me a headache. I had to hurry downstairs to get &amp;ldquo;guò zǎo&amp;rdquo; (the Wuhan term for the morning ritual of eating breakfast).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going to the Square to Dance</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/going-to-the-square-to-dance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/going-to-the-square-to-dance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As night fell, Wuhan, having passed the &amp;ldquo;Minor Heat&amp;rdquo; solar term, was somehow less scorching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The clouds in the sky were always piled thick, clump after clump, like sun umbrellas, blocking the sun from time to time. Occasionally, at dusk, the heavens would bestow a stingy shower, taming some of the fierce heat of the scalding asphalt roads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shelves outside the HotMaxx discount store were diligently displaying all kinds of beer. A 500ml can of Budweiser, nearing its expiration date, sold for only 4 yuan. There were no 330ml cans in the promotion, which seemed to suggest that people&amp;rsquo;s starting volume for beer consumption had seen a substantial increase. Although he rarely drank anymore, Linsong still bought a case. Even if he didn&amp;rsquo;t drink it, just having it chilled in the fridge and seeing the pile of beer every time he opened the door felt cooling.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Book Fair</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-book-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-book-fair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When you&amp;rsquo;re slightly tipsy, how can you refuse a chat with a talkative taxi driver?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I vaguely remember the last time was in Hong Kong. I had left a Bob Dylan concert early, otherwise I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have made it to the Mount Davis Youth Hostel before its reception closed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The old driver asked, bewildered, why I chose to stay on the mountain.
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s cheap there.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s about the same in the city, there are hotels everywhere. Factoring in this taxi fare, it&amp;rsquo;s not worth it.&amp;rdquo;
Indeed, the taxi fare that night was more expensive than a night at the youth hostel.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jousting on a Weekend Morning</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/jousting-on-a-weekend-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/jousting-on-a-weekend-morning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Friday afternoon was utterly exhausting. The client&amp;rsquo;s warehouse closed at five, so there was no time to deliver the prepped goods. After a quick discussion with the client, they agreed to a Saturday morning delivery. One final confirmation: yes, the client&amp;rsquo;s warehouse accepts deliveries on Saturdays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming out of the underground garage, Lin Song slipped on his sunglasses while waiting at a red light to make a U-turn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The barrier for the U-turn lane extended nearly to the middle of the intersection. Why not make it shorter? It was only after turning the car and climbing onto the ramp that he understood: if the barrier wasn&amp;rsquo;t extended, cars turning too early might hit the ramp&amp;rsquo;s guardrail.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Cheaper Than Cheap?</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/whats-cheaper-than-cheap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/whats-cheaper-than-cheap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Wuhan Meteorological Observatory upgraded its high-temperature warning to a red alert, with some streets reaching over 41°C (106°F). Lin Song felt like a frog being boiled in water; after being cooked for so long, he had learned to swim in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On days when the sun beat down, Lin Song would go out wearing a long-sleeved shirt, long pants, and a hat, after smearing a layer of sunscreen on his face and the back of his neck. He kept a bottle of sunscreen spray in his car year-round—a waterproof, sport-type spray that felt greasy on his arms and reflected the sunlight.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meddling in Right and Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/medding-in-right-and-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/medding-in-right-and-wrong/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lin Song was often criticized for not doing housework.
&amp;ldquo;Sigh, when it comes to anything, you just can&amp;rsquo;t rely on others.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Tonight, you&amp;rsquo;re making your own dinner.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Believe it or not, I&amp;rsquo;ll spill the coffee in your cup! All you know how to do every day is make coffee for yourself.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Lin Song was little, the leftovers on the table had to be covered with gauze food covers to keep the flies away. The now-extinct fly swatter was once a must-have in every home; almost everyone had one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Hasn&#39;t Used a Few Second-Hand Things?</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/who-hasnt-used-a-few-second-hand-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/who-hasnt-used-a-few-second-hand-things/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Even in the sweltering heat of midsummer, there can be cool mornings. The early-rising sun was blocked by the tall buildings to the east. In the community&amp;rsquo;s courtyard, a through-draft blew from north to south, wandering between the apartment buildings and the small woods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though it was long past his usual breakfast time, Lin Song wasn&amp;rsquo;t hungry at all. All told, sixteen hours had passed since last night&amp;rsquo;s dinner. Perhaps due to the heat, he still had no appetite.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love on a Little Motor Scooter</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/love-on-a-little-motor-scooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/love-on-a-little-motor-scooter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lin Song believes he is the most ill-tempered man in all of Hankou.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But living in Wuhan, what can you do? The winter is cold enough to freeze your scalp; the summer is hot enough to agitate you from the inside out. As for flying into these nameless rages, Lin Song feels it&amp;rsquo;s completely beyond his control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He remembers Wu Meili once telling him:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not the kind of person who is nice to others for no reason. You are good to me first, and then I will be good to you. If you want me to be good to you first, there&amp;rsquo;s no way.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crayfish Are Not Lobsters</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/crayfish-are-not-lobsters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/crayfish-are-not-lobsters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In 2023, a 45-year-old Brazilian businessman named Hugo Farias set a Guinness World Record by completing 366 marathons in a row. Yes, he did it on purpose—one more than the 365 days in a year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I gave up a stable career to pursue a completely unknown goal,&amp;rdquo; he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the news, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that Hugo is a successful businessman. But in Lin Song&amp;rsquo;s view, successful businessmen don&amp;rsquo;t pursue completely unknown goals. As the saying goes, &amp;ldquo;Success comes from preparation; failure comes from lack thereof.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinning Hair</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/thinning-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/thinning-hair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just three hours ago, Christian Horner resigned from his position as Team Principal and CEO of the Oracle Red Bull Racing team, effective immediately, exiting the F1 team. Twenty years, 405 races, 141 championship titles—eight drivers&amp;rsquo; championships, six constructors&amp;rsquo; championships. He was the longest-serving team principal in Red Bull&amp;rsquo;s history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An era has completely ended.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, Verstappen secured the drivers&amp;rsquo; championship for Red Bull, but the constructors&amp;rsquo; title was snatched by McLaren. The Thai and Austrian sides of Red Bull have been in constant dispute over control of the F1 team.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Down for Good</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/closing-down-for-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/closing-down-for-good/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You think it&amp;rsquo;s customer loyalty, but in reality, everyone is just fleecing you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The printer rattles off orders from Ele.me, and the ice machine is completely empty. To keep up with the pace of the iced water promotion, the only option is to buy another thirty liters of ice cubes from Meituan. In this fiery July, as JD.com joins the slaughterhouse of food delivery platforms, iced water truly flows like a river.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploding with Orders</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/exploding-with-orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/exploding-with-orders/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lin Song had absolutely no intention of going out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even in the morning, the coolest part of the day, the glaring sunlight outside his curtains made him feel an invisible wave of heat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summer is like that. You never feel hungry. Even if your empty stomach rumbles, you have no desire to eat. A couple of sips of water make you feel better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But not wanting to eat is just an illusion created by the sweltering heat. Lin Song rationally reminded himself that it was almost noon, and the task of combining two meals into one still needed to be done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pretending to Have Heatstroke</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/pretending-to-have-heatstroke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/pretending-to-have-heatstroke/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;They say today is the end of the world. And so, the 39-degree heat of Wuhan&amp;rsquo;s summer arrived especially early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weather in Wuhan today: 39 degrees Celsius. Don&amp;rsquo;t ask. Wuhan&amp;rsquo;s weather is only ever allowed to be 39 degrees. Even if the sun in the sky were to fall on your face, the temperature would still only be permitted to be 39 degrees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At a time like this, if you dared to go out under the sun and lick a utility pole by the road, you&amp;rsquo;d hear a &lt;em&gt;sizzle&lt;/em&gt;, and your tongue would be seared.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a Latte with a Heart</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/making-a-latte-with-a-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/making-a-latte-with-a-heart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lin Song took out his phone and found his instructor, Mr. Zhou, on WeChat. The map showed the location of the coffee shop he had recommended. It was over 700 meters from the bus stop, an eight-minute walk. His interview with the coffee shop owner was scheduled for 10:30 AM; he should be on time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This past Tuesday, he had finished his barista course at the training school. After the exam next Friday, he would receive his graduation certificate. Learning to make bread and coffee, he thought, was far more interesting than preparing for the &lt;em&gt;Gaokao&lt;/em&gt;. The funny thing was, even the instructors sometimes messed up, and you could actually laugh in class—something that was never allowed back in his high school.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Summer Vacation Slingshot</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-summer-vacation-slingshot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-summer-vacation-slingshot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The sky this summer was exceptionally blue. In this often-gray city, there are always a few days in the year perfect for looking up at the sky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the sun set, a crescent moon would appear simultaneously in the southern sky. It looked white and tender, with a kind of delicate posture that Lin Song found endearing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lin Song had always loved summer vacation. The break was long enough, a full two months. At the beginning of every summer, he would set a small goal for himself: to finish all his summer homework within two weeks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin or Husky?</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/qilin-or-husky/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/qilin-or-husky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The two Qilin have been crouching at the entrance of the shopping mall for twenty-four years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what material they&amp;rsquo;re coated with, but they are entirely jet-black and haven&amp;rsquo;t shown a speck of rust all these years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first, Manager Wang from the property management department told Lin Song that the two statues at the main entrance were Qilin. So, Lin Song called them Qilin. In any case, Lin Song had never seen a living Qilin, and Manager Wang was always exceptionally serious and responsible in his work. His words were worthy of Lin Song&amp;rsquo;s trust.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catching a Breeze, Enjoying the Shade</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/catching-a-breeze-enjoying-the-shade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/catching-a-breeze-enjoying-the-shade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hurry, hurry, it&amp;rsquo;s green.&amp;rdquo;
The words had barely left his lips when the pedestrian light turned red.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lin Song had a good, long sleep, a full ten hours of it. It was only after waking that he felt a chill on his back; the blanket had been bunched up under his stomach at some point. The air conditioner had been running all night, which let him sleep soundly—perhaps because he had been so exhausted the day before. He ran a hand through his thinning hair and comforted himself that sleeping an extra two hours once in a while wasn&amp;rsquo;t an extravagance. He was at an age where sleep was supposed to get shorter, so sleeping in this late felt more satisfying than eating a plate of braised pork ribs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Moon Like a Hook</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-moon-like-a-hook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-moon-like-a-hook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He woke up even earlier today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Do you know what Los Angeles looks like at four in the morning?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was only an hour later than Kobe. &lt;em&gt;Call it the time difference between Los Angeles and Hankou,&lt;/em&gt; Lin Song thought, forgiving himself as he bathed in the cool, crisp midsummer morning breeze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sign of the corner ice cream shop at the mall was lit up day and night, as if determined to adorn the city&amp;rsquo;s summer nights, which were soon to become scorching hot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Uncles&#39; First Milk Tea</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-uncles-first-milk-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-uncles-first-milk-tea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After raining all day, the sky began to clear toward evening. The setting sun cast a brilliant golden glow on the glass curtain walls of the high-rise buildings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It took Lin Song a full hour to inch his way from Yindun Street, west of Hankou Railway Station, to Jinsui Street on the east side. The square in front of the station was gridlocked with countless ride-share cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lin Song parked in the underground garage and then went to the bus stop across the road. Several bus routes went directly to Qushuilou, and from there, it was just a few minutes&amp;rsquo; walk to Liangliang Steamed Crayfish in the Wansongyuan district.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brad Pitt&#39;s Big F1 Movie</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/brad-pitts-big-f1-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/brad-pitts-big-f1-movie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The streetlights were already out, but the sky had yet to fully brighten. After the summer solstice, the days grow shorter, the nights longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It had been a long time since Lin Song had woken up this early. If he didn&amp;rsquo;t leave right away, he would never check off all the items on his to-do list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the kitchen, he could hear the pitter-patter of what might be rain striking the awning outside. Lin Song couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell if it was actually raining or just condensation dripping from an upstairs air conditioner.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fortunate Feline Cat</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/a-fortunate-feline-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/a-fortunate-feline-cat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lin Song&amp;rsquo;s cat is named Xiao Xiao, from the word &lt;em&gt;xiaosǎ&lt;/em&gt;, meaning &amp;ldquo;dashing&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;free-spirited.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This British Shorthair was a gift from the &amp;ldquo;Cat Auntie&amp;rdquo; in Building 7 of his apartment complex. The Cat Auntie keeps seventeen cats. Xiao Xiao and his three siblings were born to the same mother, and he was the runt of the litter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the Cat Auntie placed Xiao Xiao in Lin Song&amp;rsquo;s hands, she confidently told him it was a female. &amp;ldquo;Taking a cat from me,&amp;rdquo; she declared, &amp;ldquo;is like taking home a bundle of good fortune.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Night Market</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/night-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/night-market/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a four-month shutdown, the Baocheng Street Night Market was finally open again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Zhang Wanqin, are you still drinking? Time to set up your stall!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Last sip! Be right down!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lin Song, pulling his flatbed cart, habitually yelled up toward the second floor as he passed the alleyway entrance. He was always the first to arrive. Every day, once his freezer chest was settled in its usual spot, the stalls to his left and right would extend out from it like coordinates, leaving a corridor down the middle of the road for people to walk. For over twenty years, the rule had never changed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From the Main Road to a Single-Plank Bridge</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/from-the-main-road-to-a-single-plank-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/from-the-main-road-to-a-single-plank-bridge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There was a moderately sized coffee industry exhibition at the International Expo Center over the weekend. Lin Song had long lost his enthusiasm for joining crowds; whether in his daily life or in business, he instinctively resisted excessive exertion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lately, however, his business seemed to be turning a corner. As the May weather grew warmer, the coffee shop&amp;rsquo;s losses narrowed. It looked as if with a bit more diligent effort, profitability was within reach. His wholesale coffee bean business had also picked up. Although the cafés he had personally cultivated as clients were closing down one after another, his distribution channel customers had persevered, with sales volumes and turnover rates actually increasing. And so, on mornings when he was awoken by the sunlight, Lin Song felt a long-lost glimmer of anticipation for the future. This glimmer was just enough to coax him out of the house.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wrong Roads Taken Are Still Roads</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-wrong-roads-taken-are-still-roads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-wrong-roads-taken-are-still-roads/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The rain from last night, neither too heavy nor too light, had finally ceased before dawn. The air was filled with the damp, earthy smell of the soil, mingled with the unique clamor of a city awakening. The wet asphalt glistened under the sparse streetlights, reflecting a cool, clean light. A news alert popped up on Lin Song&amp;rsquo;s phone: &lt;em&gt;The U.S. had bombed Iran.&lt;/em&gt; The world was vast, a stage for distant gunfire and conflict, like a movie that had nothing to do with him. Lin Song&amp;rsquo;s world, however, was small—so small it was confined to the path leading to the breakfast shop. Today, the city&amp;rsquo;s high school entrance exams were finally over. The long period of noise and tension seemed to have found a moment of respite along with the final bell.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Long Has It Been Since I Was Soaked by a Downpour?</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/how-long-has-it-been-since-i-was-soaked-by-a-downpout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/how-long-has-it-been-since-i-was-soaked-by-a-downpout/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Wuhan, the last ten days of every June are always a time of torrential downpours. It’s as if their frenzied nature has offended the Dragon King; the relentless rain shrouds the city for more than ten days straight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A thousand years ago, Hankou was still a marsh. In the rainy summers, the wild ducks were happiest. Back then, there was endless rain from the sky and an inexhaustible supply of small fish in the lakes. As all of nature flourished, all the wild ducks had to do was dart about, twisting their nimble necks and eating nonstop. When full, they would nap under the shade of a tree. Waking at dusk, they would rush into the ponds and continue eating. The wild ducks in the Hankou marsh grew fat and plump, their feathers glossy and sleek.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Childhood Without Labubu</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/a-childhood-without-labubu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/a-childhood-without-labubu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Lin Song’s childhood memories, summer vacation was intrinsically linked to his grandmother and the fragrance of the earth. Every July, when the school’s white walls were scorched by the blazing sun and the teacher on the podium wrote the final stroke with a piece of chalk to announce the start of the holiday, his heart had already flown to the small village nestled deep in the lake district. His father would always drive the old &amp;ldquo;Jiefang&amp;rdquo; (Liberation) brand truck from his work unit, taking him to his grandmother&amp;rsquo;s doorstep amidst a roaring &amp;ldquo;chug-chug-chug&amp;rdquo; and clouds of dust. Lin Song had once asked how much coal the truck could carry at once. His father held up five rough fingers and said proudly, &amp;ldquo;Five tons. Enough to keep a large courtyard of families warm for an entire winter.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boss, I Have to Pay My Rent Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-road-to-the-inrerview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-road-to-the-inrerview/</guid>
      <description>The Road to the Interview</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fill It Up with 95</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/fill-it-up-with-95/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/fill-it-up-with-95/</guid>
      <description>A Muggy Night</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pulse of Hankou</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-pulse-of-hankou/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-pulse-of-hankou/</guid>
      <description>A History of Ascending and Descending Commercial Powers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Weakening Dollar</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-weakening-dollar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-weakening-dollar/</guid>
      <description>A Former Beacon Losing Its Luster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hanzheng Street</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/hanzheng-street/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/hanzheng-street/</guid>
      <description>The Bustling Hub of Merchants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Difference Between Earning Money and Investing</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/the-difference-between-earning-money-and-investing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/the-difference-between-earning-money-and-investing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When you leave home punctually from Monday to Friday, take the crowded subway to the busy office, day after day, what you anticipate is the salary your boss pays you each month. Regardless of your skills or how much energy and enthusiasm you invest, the final salary you receive is generally in line with your expectation – not significantly more, nor noticeably less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the salary your boss provides, you might treat friends to a special seafood meal when a restaurant has a promotion. On weekends, shedding your stiff work attire for a comfortable T-shirt, you might visit a street bar for a drink and offer polite applause to a singer you enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jianghan Road</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/jianghan-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/jianghan-road/</guid>
      <description>The Pioneer Road of Modern Real Estate Development in Hankou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fading Gold</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/fading-gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/fading-gold/</guid>
      <description>The Reflection of Value and the Game of Safe Haven</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jianghan Customs House in Wuhan</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/jianghan-customs-house-in-wuhan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/jianghan-customs-house-in-wuhan/</guid>
      <description>Hankou&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;Foreign Wharf&amp;#39;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkshire Hathaway&#39;s Stock Price</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/berkshire_hathaway_sotck_price/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/berkshire_hathaway_sotck_price/</guid>
      <description>Valuation in the Post-Buffett Era</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gates&#39; Wealth and Legacy</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/gates_wealth_and_legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/gates_wealth_and_legacy/</guid>
      <description>The Challenge and Philosophy of Spending Down the Foundation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once Upon a Time in Hankou</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/once_upon_a_time_in_hankou/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/once_upon_a_time_in_hankou/</guid>
      <description>Hankou Business Latecomers Take Advantage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consulate</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/consulate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/consulate/</guid>
      <description>There are some foreign consulates in Wuhan (including Hankou area)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acceptance</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/acceptance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/acceptance/</guid>
      <description>The foundation of the modern financial system is credit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Crane Tower</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/yellow_crane_tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/yellow_crane_tower/</guid>
      <description>Poetry of the Tang Dynasty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;hankou.com is an online humanities space dedicated to recording and observing the urban changes and citizens&amp;rsquo; lives in Wuhan (especially Hankou). We explore the unique temperament and pulse of the city through in-depth essays, stories and comments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In every crowded land, I hear the quiet voices of people and see the ignored fate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In that faraway place</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/insights/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/insights/introduction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;in-the-north-sea-there-is-a-peng-whose-wings-are-like-clouds-hanging-from-the-sky&#34;&gt;In the North Sea there is a Peng, whose wings are like clouds hanging from the sky&amp;hellip;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a story that will unfold here. If you have &lt;strong&gt;patience&lt;/strong&gt;, I will tell you the story.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I thought was going on before, now seems not to be so natural.&lt;br&gt;
Only when you meet again and again, you can see it more &lt;strong&gt;clearly&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/business-costs/office-rent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/business-costs/office-rent/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/regulations/reg-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/regulations/reg-overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/about/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/about/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hankou2025@gmail.com&#34;&gt;hankou2025@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://hankou.com/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hankou.com/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last updated: July 13, 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection,
use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You
about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the
Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with
this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
